<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Computational Demonology</string>
    <string name="cd_intro">Computational Demonology is the science of using maths and algorithms to interact
        with the fundamental fabric of reality, particularly the borders between universes. Over the centuries,
       many mathematicians have accidentally discovered certain numbers and ways of processing those numbers which
        are capable of breaching those borders and bringing \"things\" from other universes into ours. These \"things\"
        are the creatures of myth: the demons, angels, spirits, ghosts, and dark energies of old stories and night terrors.
        Computer scientists and mathematicians working in secret have studied the algorithms and collected the
        \"beneficial\" formulae together for use in fighting those which are more... disturbing. A select few are
        presented below.  If you find yourself in certain... situations, they may be able to help. Please use with
        caution, and think pleasant thoughts.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="code">CASE CODE GAME INDEX OPERATION INCIDENT SCENARIO SEQUENCE PLAN PROJECT</string>
    <string name="nouns">BLUE RED GREEN BLACK VIOLET WHITE MAUVE CODEX PENAL BOVINE EQUUS FELINE CANINE
    NIGHTMARE salt scar wound bone
    amorphous  indefinite  shapeless beguile  deceive caprice  impulse cascade  steep waterfall cashmere  fine  delicate
wool chrysalis  its soft brown color coalesce  unite fuse
crepuscular  dim  crystalline desultory  half-hearted  meandering diaphanous  gauzy
dulcet  sweet ebullient  enthusiastic effervescent  bubbly elision  omission enchanted  charmed encompass  surround
enrapture  delighted ephemeral  fleeting epiphany  revelation epitome  embodiment ethereal  celestial
unworldly  immaterial etiquette  proper conduct evanescent  fleeting evocative  suggestive exuberant  abundant
unrestrained  outsize felicity  happiness  pleasantness filament  thread  strand halcyon  care-free idyllic
contentedly pleasing incorporeal  incandescent  glowing  radiant  brilliant  zealous ineffable
indescribable  unspeakable inexorable  relentless insouciance  nonchalance iridescent  luster languid  slow  listless
lassitude  fatigue lilt  cheerful buoyant song movement lithe  flexible  graceful lullaby  soothing song
luminescence  dim chemical organic light mellifluous smooth cloudy moisture virtual obstacle murmur
        sound myriad  great number nebulous  indistinct opulent  ostentatious penumbra  shade
shroud  fringe plethora  abundance quiescent  peaceful quintessential purely representative radiant
glowing redolent  aromatic  evocative resonant  echoing  evocative resplendent  shining rhapsodic  intensely emotional
sapphire  bluish purple scintilla  trace serendipitous  chance serene  peaceful somnolent  drowsy  sleep
inducing sonorous  loud  impressive  imposing spherical  ball-like  globular sublime  exalted  transcendent succulent
 suffuse  flushed  full susurration  whispering symphony  harmonious assemblage talisman  charm
magical device tessellated  checkered in pattern tranquility  peacefulness vestige  trace zenith  highest point ugly
cacophony  confused noise cataclysm  flood  catastrophe  upheaval chafe  irritate  abrade coarse  common  crude
rough  harsh cynical  distrustful  self-interested decrepit   disgust  aversion  distaste grimace
expression disgust pain grotesque  distorted  bizarre harangue  rant hirsute  hairy hoarse  harsh  grating leech
parasite  maladroit  clumsy obstreperous  unruly rancid
repugnant  distasteful repulsive  disgusting shriek  sharp  screeching  shrill  high-pitched  shun  avoid
ostracize slaughter  butcher  carnage unctuous  smug  ingratiating visceral  crude  anatomically graphic
unbearable intolerable</string>
    <string name="htmlparse">You can\'t parse [X]HTML with regex. Because HTML can\'t be parsed by regex. Regex is not a tool that can be used to
correctly parse HTML. As I have answered in HTML-and-regex questions here so many times before, the use of regex will
not allow you to consume HTML. Regular expressions are a tool that is insufficiently sophisticated to understand the
constructs employed by HTML. HTML is not a regular language and hence cannot be parsed by regular expressions. Regex
queries are not equipped to break down HTML into its meaningful parts. so many times but it is not getting to me. Even
enhanced irregular regular expressions as used by Perl are not up to the task of parsing HTML. You will never make me
crack. HTML is a language of sufficient complexity that it cannot be parsed by regular expressions. Even Jon Skeet
cannot parse HTML using regular expressions. Every time you attempt to parse HTML with regular expressions, the unholy
child weeps the blood of virgins, and Russian hackers pwn your webapp. Parsing HTML with regex summons tainted souls
into the realm of the living. HTML and regex go together like love, marriage, and ritual infanticide. The
&lt;center&gt; cannot hold it is too late. The force of regex and HTML together in the same conceptual space will
destroy your mind like so much watery putty. If you parse HTML with regex you are giving in to Them and their
blasphemous ways which doom us all to inhuman toil for the One whose Name cannot be expressed in the Basic Multilingual
Plane, he comes. HTML-plus-regexp will liquify the n​erves of the sentient whilst you observe, your psyche withering in
the onslaught of horror. Rege̿̔̉x-based HTML parsers are the cancer that is killing StackOverflow it is too late it is
too late we cannot be saved the trangession of a chi͡ld ensures regex will consume all living tissue (except for HTML
which it cannot, as previously prophesied) dear lord help us how can anyone survive this scourge using regex to parse
HTML has doomed humanity to an eternity of dread torture and security holes using regex as a tool to process HTML
establishes a breach between this world and the dread realm of c͒ͪo͛ͫrrupt entities (like SGML entities, but more
corrupt) a mere glimpse of the world of reg​ex parsers for HTML will ins​tantly transport a programmer\'s consciousness
into a world of ceaseless screaming, he comes, the pestilent slithy regex-infection wil​l devour your HT​ML parser,
application and existence for all time like Visual Basic only worse he comes he comes do not fi​ght he com̡e̶s, ̕h̵i​s
un̨ho͞ly radiańcé destro҉ying all enli̍̈́̂̈́ghtenment, HTML tags lea͠ki̧n͘g fr̶ǫm ̡yo​͟ur eye͢s̸ ̛l̕ik͏e liq​uid pain,
the song of re̸gular exp​ression parsing will exti​nguish the voices of mor​tal man from the sp​here I can see it can
you see ̲͚̖͔̙î̩́t̲͎̩̱͔́̋̀ it is beautiful t​he final snuffing of the lie​s of Man ALL IS LOŚ͖̩͇̗̪̏̈́T ALL I​S LOST the
pon̷y he comes he c̶̮omes he comes the ich​or permeates all MY FACE MY FACE ᵒh god no NO NOO̼O​O NΘ stop the
an​*̶͑̾̾​̅ͫ͏̙̤g͇̫͛͆̾ͫ̑͆l͖͉̗̩̳̟̍ͫͥͨe̠̅s ͎a̧͈͖r̽̾̈́͒͑e n​ot rè̑ͧ̌aͨl̘̝̙̃ͤ͂̾̆ ZA̡͊͠͝LGΌ ISͮ̂҉̯͈͕̹̘̱ TO͇̹̺ͅƝ̴ȳ̳ TH̘Ë͖́̉ ͠P̯͍̭O̚​N̐Y̡ H̸̡̪̯ͨ͊̽̅̾̎Ȩ̬̩̾͛ͪ̈́̀́͘ ̶̧̨̱̹̭̯ͧ̾ͬC̷̙̲̝͖ͭ̏ͥͮ͟Oͮ͏̮̪̝͍M̲̖͊̒ͪͩͬ̚̚͜Ȇ̴̟̟͙̞ͩ͌͝S̨̥̫͎̭ͯ̿̔̀ͅ  </string>
    <string name="lovecraft">Hastur Ithaqua Nyarlathotep Zhar Lloigor	Cyäegha Nyogtha Shub-Niggurath Tsathoggua	Aphoom-Zhah Cthugha	Cthulhu Dagon
Ghatanothoa Mother Hydra Zoth-Ommog Abhoth Aiueb Gnshal Azathoth Azhorra-Tha The Blackness from the Stars The Cloud-Thing C\'thalpa Cxaxukluth Daoloth
 Darkness D’endrrah Ghroth The Hydra Ialdagorth Kaajh\'Kaalbh Lu-Kthu Mh\'ithrha Mlandoth and Mril Thorion Mother of
 Pus The Nameless Mist Ngyr-Korath Nyarlathotep Nyctelios Ny-Rakath Olkoth Shabbith-Ka Shub-Niggurath Star Mother
 Suc\'Naath Tru\'nembra Tulzscha Ubbo-Sathla Uvhash Xa\'ligha Xexanoth Ycnàgnnisssz Yhoundeh Yibb-Tstll Yidhra
 Yog-Sothoth Yomagn\'tho Elder Gods List Bast Kthanid Orryx Oztalun Nodens Shavalyoth Ulthar Vorvadoss Yad-Thaddag
 Yaggdytha </string>
    <string name="lovecraft2">Yog-Sothoth knows the gate. Yog-Sothoth is the gate. Yog-Sothoth is the key and guardian of the gate.
        Past, present, future, all are one in Yog-Sothoth. He knows where the Old Ones broke through of old, and where They shall break
through again. He knows where They have trod earth\'s fields, and where They still tread them, and why no one can behold
Them as They tread. ph\'nglui mglw\'nafh Cthulhu R\'lyeh wgah\'nagl fhtagn. ph\'nglui mglw\'nafh Cthulhu R\'lyeh wgah\'nagl fhtagn.
That is not dead which can eternal lie, And with strange aeons even death may die. All that the universe has to hold of
        horror, and even the skies of spring and the flowers of summer must ever afterward be poison to me.
        The other gods! The other gods! The gods of the outer hells that guard the feeble gods of earth!...
        Look away... Go back... Do not see! Do not see!"
    </string>
    <string name="hwords">destroy kill avenge reap exterminate unmake sweep away kill extirpate wipe
        pulverise pulverize rase end dilapidate disassemble self-destruct
break apart eliminate fracture take down break up dismantle take apart undo tear interdict demyelinate
self-destroy demolish  level pull down destruct uproot extinguish raze root out eradicate
evil vile wicked base corrupt immoral dishonest sinful heinous depraved profane iniquitous ungodly blood bile
    </string>
    <string name="endwords">all is lost,oh god oh god oh god,no more,the end,shall rise,has fallen to,
        my mind,no one left,death is all,sleep no more,don\'t blink,eternal sleep,he comes,no escape,no rest,
    the abyss is staring back, the abyss, nothingness encompasses, the angles are not real, my face my face,
    nothing is left</string>
</resources>
